<resources>
    <string name="app_name">SantoriniGuide</string>

    <string name="vulcano"><b>Departure point:</b> Ormos Athinios, Greece<br />
<b>Start Time:</b> 10:00 AM<br />
<b>Santorini Volcano</b> <i>1h30min</i> - walk an ascending path to the crater of the still active volcano<br />
<b>Nea Kameni</b> <i>1h30min</i> - guided tour to the Lava islet of Nea Kameni<br />
<b>Palea Kameni </b><i>30min</i> - jump off the boat into warm thermal waters<br />
<b>Thirassia </b><i>1h30min</i> - visit village of Manolas on donkey or walk winding stairs<br />
<br />
The active volcano lies underwater, but everyone can visit and wonder the two formed by black lava islands of Palaia Kameni and Nea Kameni. You can explore the imposing volcanic scenery and admire its wild beauty, see its crater, stroll around and touch the black lava rocks and certainly get this unique feeling of hiking on a steaming Volcano.<br />
In addition, at the foothills of Palaia Kameni island, there are the famous Hot Springs, waters full of sulfur that are known for their therapeutic effects. You can enjoy yourself with a different mud bath while gazing at the amazing view of the Caldera that lies opposite.
    </string>

    <string name="fira"><b>Fira Town</b>
Fira is the beautiful capital of the island and the biggest and most cosmopolitan settlement of Santorini. It is located in the western edge of the island, opposite the volcano and the two volcanic islands, Palaia Kammeni and Nea Kammeni that lie in the sea.

Access to Fira, besides the road routes from the port and the airport, is also feasible by cable car or through a donkey path from the port, for those seeking a traditional experience.

Fira is a combination of natural beauty, social life, night life, and shopping, where you can feel the liveliness of the island and where all the action takes place. What makes it so ravishing is the Caldera view that leaves visitors speechless anytime of the day. A walk to the scenic alleys during the daytime will fill you with harmony, while at night you can find yourself in the middle of a big party. There is a wealth of restaurants, cafes, bars and clubs where you can relax and enjoy the tremendous view or dance and have fun. It actually owns the greatest dining out and entertainment selection of the island and the largest shopping center, too. Moreover, there are many clothes shops, gift shops, souvenir shops, supermarkets and other facilities for every need.

Among the wonderful landmarks, the Megaro Gyzi Cultural Center that presents a variety of collections and organizes several cultural events, like concerts and theatrical performances, and the two cathedrals of Fira are worth visiting. Two of the exceptional museums of Santorini are situated in Fira as well, the Archaeological Museum of Thera and the Museum of Prehistoric Thera, which offer a multitude of relics and historic items from the whole island. In addition, in close distance to Fira, in Kontochori village, there is the Folklore Museum of Emmanuel A. Lignos which holds six rooms-exhibitions that depict the way of life in the 20th century.

An abundance of accommodation options can be found in the capital of Santorini, from luxurious hotels with an outstanding caldera view to a camping area for an alternative stay that will satisfy nature lovers.
    </string>

    <string name="oia"><b>Oia</b> is located 11 km away from Fira and is a pedestrian town. Most of the visitors come here to admire its unique architecture, captains houses, Blue Domes, cave houses and the sunset. You can see crowds of people here any time of the day, for its a must to see if you are in Santorini.
    </string>

    <string name="akrotiri"><b>Akrotiri</b> came to an abrupt end in approximately 1613 BC with a catastrophic volcanic eruption that buried the Bronze Age settlement in a carpet of ash. Beginning in 1967, excavations of the Minoan town revealed buildings, drainage systems, and pottery, but no human remains or gold valuables, indicating locals had time to flee before disaster hit.
    </string>

    <string name="akrotiri_ruins"><h2>Archaeological bus tour to Akrotiri excavations and Red beach</h2></string>

    <string name="Thirassia">The island of <b>Thirassia</b> is located adjacent to Santorini; in fact, it was once a part of it.
The volcanic eruption that occurred at around 1500 BC snapped Santorini off and Thirassia emerged. Nowadays, Thirassia is a virgin island, still untouched by tourism and modern lifestyle.
The island is only 9 sq. km in size and has only 150 permanent inhabitants.
Manolas village is the capital, while other settlements include Korfos, Riva, and Potamos. A walk through villages can also be a wonderful experience, as in front of the houses lie gardens with colorful blossoms.
    </string>

    <string name="booktrip">Book Trip Here</string>
    <string name="booktripnow">Book Your Trip Now</string>
    <string name="booknow">Book Now</string>
    <string name="showdetails">Show Details</string>
    <string name="calderabeach">Caldera Beach</string>
    <string name="redbeach">Red Beach</string>
    <string name="erosbeach">Eros Beach</string>
    <string name="whitebeach">White Beach</string>
    <string name="sendemail">SEND AN EMAIL</string>
    <string name="bookingdetails">BOOKING DETAILS</string>
    <string name="sendsms">SEND SMS QUERY</string>
    <string name="checkinlist">CHECK IN LIST IN THERA (FIRA)</string>
    <string name="OldHarbour">Visit Old Harbour</string>
    <string name="ViewSunset">View Sunset</string>
    <string name="brosPub">Visit 2Bros Pub</string>
    <string name="stairs">Karavolades Stairs</string>
    <string name="eatSuvlaki">Eat Souvlaki</string>
    <string name="hike">Do Fira-Oia Hike</string>
    <string name="getdirections">GET DIRECTIONS</string>
    <string name="transport">TRANSPORT</string>
    <string name="beaches">BEACHES</string>
    <string name="adventures">ADVENTURES</string>
    <string name="santorinitips">SANTORINII TIPS</string>
    <string name="mytodolist">MY TO DO LIST</string>
    <string name="restaurants">RESTAURANTS</string>
    <string name="triproutemap">TRIP ROUTE MAP</string>
    <string name="bookfiraoia">BOOK FIRA - OIA HIKING TRIP</string>
    <string name="bookme">BOOK ME</string>
    <string name="callforinfo">CALL FOR MORE INFO</string>
    <string name="car">CAR</string>
    <string name="quad">QUAD</string>
    <string name="scooter">SCOOTER</string>
    <string name="buggy">BUGGY</string>
    <string name="todolist">Your TODO list</string>
    <string name="savelist">SAVE LIST</string>
    <string name="showtodolist">SHOW MY TODO LIST</string>
    <string name="takepic">TAKE PIC</string>
    <string name="attractions">ATTRACTIONS</string>

</resources>